《嘻哈帝国》前情提要
Previously on Empire...
帝国娱乐公司已经
Empire Entertainment has filed
正式提交上市申请
to become a publicly traded company.
拜托了  贾马尔  我需要你帮忙
Come on, Jamal, I need your help.
跟我无关
I don't care.
你觉得我还会让你利用我多久
How long did you think I would just let you use me?
你的生命里还没有那个特别的她吗
There's no special girl in your life?
没有特别的人
No one special.
对于患有双极情感障碍的人来说
For someone who's bipolar,
取消和医生的预约可是性命攸关的
cancelling a doctor's appointment is life-threatening.
-不给  -给我
- No! - Give it back!
我也在努力翻盘  艾儿
I am fighting for a comeback, too, Elle.
我也是破釜沉舟  没有退路
It is do or die for me, too.
我是马尔科姆·德沃
I'm Malcolm DeVeaux,
帝国娱乐的新安保主管
Empire's new head of security.
我已经感觉更安全了  德沃先生
I feel safer already, Mr. DeVeaux.
-我还有多长时间  -三年
- How long I got? - Three years.
梅森医生  我们怎么能确定这是安全的
Dr. Mason, how do we know that this is gonna be safe?
这还是试验性药物
It's an experimental drug.
-但是  -没有它我就会死
- But... - I am dead without it.
怎么了  奥利维亚  你来这里干什么
What's up, Olivia? What are you doing here?
她想要见见她的爸爸
She wanted to meet her daddy.
帝国娱乐2015年投资商展示演出
成败都在这场投资商展示演出  弗农
This investor showcase is make or break for us, Vernon.
千万不能有任何闪失
I mean, nothing can go wrong.
埃里克
Eric...
我们需要更多高科技
We need more technology.
-给我加上全息摄影  -是  老板
- I mean, serious holograms. - Okay, boss.
我还听说
Also got word that, um,
奥利维亚  那个孩子的母亲
Olivia, the baby mama?
不  是他前妻
No, his ex-wife.
随便你怎么称呼她
Whatever you want to call her-- anyway,
她从09年起就住在圣路易斯
she's been down in St. Louis since '09,
找了份美发师的工作  一直没有再婚
working as a hairdresser, never got remarried...
那姑娘是个大问题  卢修斯
That girl is a problem, Lucious.
都是你害的贾马尔  她到底想怎样
You did this to Jamal. Now, what does she want?
她说她想给孩子找个爸
She wants a father for her kid is what she said.
总之  她的职业是美发师
Anyway, she's working as a hairdresser.
跟她同居那男人经常打她
Living with some dude who put his hands on her,
她为此申请了保护令
so she got an order of protection against him,
报警什么的  你明白吧
the police, all that nonsense, you know?
你怎么能逼自己的儿子娶那女孩
How could you make your son marry that girl?
怎么可以那样逼他
How could you force him to do that?
他当时才18  还是个孩子
He was 18; a baby.
现在她说自己有他的孩子
Now, she's claiming she has his baby.
你怎么知道那孩子不是他的
Well, how do you know it's not his baby?
想有孩子得先做爱啊  卢修斯
You got to have sex to make a baby, Lucious.
拜托
Come on.
不管怎么说
Either way,
我们都得解决这件事
we still gonna have to deal with it.
无论用何种手段
One way or another.
-你还好吗  -没事  我没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah, I'm good.
美国新二人音乐组合
我刚和MKTO的经纪人通完电话
I just got off with MKTO's managers.
他们得缩短南美巡演
They would have to cut the South American tour short
才能来参加展示演出  所以他们想
in order to make the showcase, so they want
给巴西粉丝办一个
a promo contest to send out
竞争一百个演出观众席的宣传活动
100 of their Brazilian fans.
不行  演出仅限潜在投资者入内
No, this is for prospective investors only.
马尔科姆说这次演出的安全风险太大
Malcolm says it's a huge security risk.
不许粉丝和媒体进场
And no fans, no press.
咱还有问题要解决  卢修斯
We still got a problem, Lucious.
马文·蒙切尔正在...
Hi! Marvin Menchel is...
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我们得讨论一下展示演出的预算
We need to go over the budget for the showcase.
银行只能...
The bank is onlly...
你不能一直回避问题
You can't keep avoiding this!
很好  谢谢  好的  再见
Fantastic. Thank you. Okay, bye.
老爸  晚餐预约好了
Dad, we are on for dinner.
什么...跟我说说这个人
What's... tell me about this guy.
他叫特里·席勒  60多岁
Uh, Terry Schiller, late 60s,
掌管着全国最大基金之一
manages one of the biggest funds in the country.
手头有好几十个亿
Billions at his fingertips.
那如果能提前拉他入伙意味着什么
So, an early commitment from him would mean what?
能极大提升公司的估值
A huge boost in the company's valuation.
你没事吧
You all right?
-没事  -好的
- Yeah. Yeah. - Okay, okay.
我们得把他请来看展示演出  爸
We need to get him to the showcase, Dad.
吸引他的最好方式就是
The way to appeal to him is
通过家庭  他很顾家
through family-- he's a real family guy, right?
他今晚和我们共进晚餐就是因为
The reason he's coming to dinner with us tonight
他女儿曾是朗达在沃顿商学院时的舍友
is because his daughter roomed with Rhonda at Wharton.
帝国娱乐就是个大家庭
Well, Empire is family.
这就是我们的卖点
I mean, that's what we're selling.
家庭就是整场展示演出的主题
Family is the whole showcase.
那就像我说的  卢修斯  你有麻烦了
Then like I said, Lucious, you got a problem.
贾马尔和哈基姆  他俩已经不能
Jamal and Hakeem-- they can't stand to be
共处一室了  更别说共同登台了
in the same room together, let alone on the same stage.
听着  他俩之间的矛盾
Look... this beef they got between each other,
不会轻易化解
it ain't dying.
我们黑香蕉餐厅见
I'll meet you at La Banana Noire.
-八点行吗  -好的
- 8 o'clock? - Yeah.
不仅如此  贾马尔已经快疯了
And on top of that, Jamal is going damn crazy.
你为啥逼他娶什么脑残伴唱女
Why would you make him marry some stupid-ass backup singer?
害得现在我们得对付这个孩子她妈
Now we got to deal with her baby mama...
够了  琦琦
Enough, Cookie!
嘻 哈 帝 国
第一季  第七集
卢修斯  能听到我说话吗
Lucious, can you hear me?
卢修斯  挺住  我们会尽快
Lucious, come on, we're going to get you
把你送到医院
to the hospital as soon as possible.
你还好吗  卢修斯
Are you okay, Lucious?
卢修斯
Lucious!
他昏倒多久了
How long has he been out?
最后一次进食是什么时候
When did he last eat?
他以前这样昏倒过吗
Has he lost consciousness before?
-小心点  -好  扶好了
- Be careful! - All right, we're good.
-你干什么  -我是他老婆
- What are you doing? - I'm his wife.
-前妻  -她马上就要成为前妻了
- Ex-wife. - She's his soon-to-be ex-wife.
到底谁陪同他去医院
I just need to know who's gonna ride with him.
-谢谢  -走  我们去打车
- Thank you. - Come on. We'll take a cab.
好了  走了  伙计们
Here we go. Let's go, guys.
迈克尔  你为什么要这样做
Michael, why are you doing all of this?
因为这就是你想要的  贾马尔
Because this is what you want, Jamal.
甚至不能当着我的面说
Couldn't even tell it to my face.
我得看节目才知道  "没有特别的人"
I had to hear it on the radio: "Nobody special"?
我说没有特别的女孩
I said no special girl!
是啊  你觉得我听到这话会是什么心情
Yeah, and how do you think that made me feel, huh?
听你向全世界这样宣告
Listening to you say that in front of the whole world!
现在你生命中确实有了一个特别的女孩
You know you do have a special girl in your life.
你女儿
A daughter.
现在结束更好  不然等到以后...
It's better to end this now before I have to...
不仅要离开你  还要离开一个孩子
walk out on you and a kid.
那孩子不是我的
The kid can't be mine.
我跟那女人就睡了一次
I slept with that girl once.
一次就够了
Well, once is all it takes.
-我的王子  我爱你  -别这么叫我
- Oh, príncipe, you know that I love you... - No, don't call me that!
你不爱我
You don't love me.
我爱你
I love you.
但你爱的却是你的音乐
But you're in love with your music.
你心里容不下别人了
You don't have room for anyone else.
我一直记得莎拉第一次
I'll never forget the first time
带你来过感恩节的情景
Sarah brought you for Thanksgiving.
我当时紧张得都吃不下东西
I was so nervous I couldn't even eat.
你家太美了  我的天
I mean, your home is so beautiful. Oh, my God.
等等  爸  让我先跟他说说
Hold on, Dad. Hold on one second while I fill him in, okay?
席勒先生  恐怕我有个坏消息
Mr. Schiller, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
我父亲的飞机在巴尔的摩紧急迫降
My father's jet had to make an emergency landing in Baltimore.
其中的一个引擎着火了
One of the engines caught fire.
他没事  就是很抱歉不能赶来
Now, he's okay, but he just, he feels terrible.
他想跟您说话
He'd like to speak with you.
特里  抱歉
Hey, Terry... sorry.
真不好意思和你说
I can't tell you, man.
该死的飞机
You know, these damn planes.
你没出事就好
Well, I'm glad you're okay.
我很乐意与你风度翩翩的儿子
And I'm delighted to spend the evening with your
还有他美丽的妻子度过这个夜晚
charming son and his beautiful wife.
我会好好听他们说  卢修斯
And I'll hear them out, Lucious.
不过我之前跟安德鲁说过
But frankly, as I told Andre in advance,
席勒基金从没有
the Schiller Fund has never been
涉足过娱乐产业
drawn to entertainment companies.
这一行太不稳定了
They're too volatile.
特里  哪怕你不打算投资
Terry, even if you decide not to invest,
也请来看演出  我向你保证
come and enjoy the concert. I promise you
这会是一场空前精彩的演出
you will not see another one like it for a while.
-好吧  -好  回头再聊
- All right. - All right. Later.
天呐
Oh, my...
-你还好吗  护士  -我在这
- You okay? Nurse! Nurse! - I'm here.
谢谢  先生
Thank you, sir.
先生  请翻身
Sir, just turn over...
这一切都是为了你  宝儿
It's all for you, "Bae."
著名美食节目厨师  此处为本人客串
你的专属罗比大厨
Your own personal private Chef Roble.
好好享受吧
Enjoy it.
宝儿  什么是宝儿
"Bae"? What is a "Bae"?
就是宝贝的意思
It means "Babe."
老兄
Bro...
看起来你这位佳人
seems like the lady's on a completely
完全没有享受到啊  不过
different date than you are, but,
如果那道鸡不能让她回心转意
if that chicken right there doesn't turn that around,
我真不知道还有什么能挽回她的心了
I don't know what will.
这是送你的
This is for you.
这是什么
What is it?
打开看看
Open it.
-怎么了  -你没搞错吧
- What? - You got to be joking.
你想让我带上你的名牌
You want to brand me with your name?
可却不想带我出现在公众场合
But you don't want to take me out in public?
我可不是你养的金丝雀  哈基姆
I'm not your backstreet slut, Hakeem.
你得像对待那个女孩一样对待我
Treat me like you treat that girl.
你为什么总说提安娜
Why you keep talking about Tiana?
你知道她什么也不算
You know she wasn't nothing to me.
那只是为了专辑销量和炒作罢了
It was for record sales and buzz.
换了是你也会这么做的
That's what you got to do in my position.
告诉我你想要什么
Just tell me what you want...
我会照做的
and I'll do anything.
你下次表演是什么时候
When are you performing next?
宝贝  不行
Baby, I can't.
那是用来募资的私人演出
It's a private thing for money folks.
公开上市的投资者们会去现场
IPO investors gonna be there.
我把你放到贵宾席上
How about I just put you on the VIP list...
就当你是投资者  怎么样
as a private investor?
你是说
So...
让我隐藏身份吗
you mean, like, incognito?
这回先保持低调
Yeah, I mean, we keep it on the DL this time.
我保证下次  我和你
Next time, it's me and you.
就会手挽手走在一起
Arm in arm, promise.
来吧
Come on.
医生
Hi, Doctor.
谢谢你能过来
Thank you for coming.
她来这里做什么
What the hell is she doing here?
梅森医生呢
Where's Dr. Mason?
我找了沙哈尼医生
I called Dr. Shahani.
我要的是梅森医生
I want Dr. Mason here!
卢瑟·梅森
Luther Mason...
他连医生都算不上
I can't even call him "Doctor."
他两年前因为拿一个病人做实验
Had his license revoked two years ago
被吊销行医执照
for doing to another patient
如今又在你身上又故技重施
what he's now doing to you.
他在救我的命
He's saving my life.
不幸的是  恰恰相反
Sadly, the opposite is true.
你的谷丙转氨酶和谷草转氨酶都升高了
Your ALT and your AST levels are elevated,
你的肝脏已经出现了初步损伤
and you're in the early stages of liver damage.
这些可不是渐冻症的症状
These aren't symptoms of ALS.
都是那个江湖骗子的药导致的
That charlatan's drugs are doing this.
我正在好转
I'm getting better.
这是他们在俄罗斯研究出的突破性疗法
It's a breakthrough treatment they've got in Russia.
他们的研究结果非常超前
They're so far ahead.
食品和药物管理局相比起来太落后了
The FDA is behind the curve.
这个所谓的俄式突破性疗法
Okay, well, this Russian so-called breakthrough
比你的疾病还要致命  卢修斯
is killing you faster than your disease is, Lucious.
那是毒药  你明白了吗
It's poison. Do you understand?
-渐冻症无药可治  -滚出去
- There is no cure for ALS. - Get out of here!
告诉你此病有药可医
And anyone who tries to tell you that there is--
并以此借口骗你钱的人是在犯罪
and takes your money while they're at it-- is a criminal.
你听明白了吗
Really, do you understand?
给我滚出去
Get the hell out of here!
医生  拜托了
Doctot, please.
里面怎么了
What's going on in there?
你是家属吗
Are you family?
我是他前妻
I used to be married to the man.
给他生了三个孩子
I gave him three sons.
这还不算家属吗
That should be family enough.
抱歉  你不能进去
I'm sorry I can't let you in.
来听听帝国娱乐体育管理部的情况
Let's hear from Empire Sports Management Division.
帝国精英体育成就显著
Empire Elite Sports rules.
我们旗下有NBA首轮选秀的六名球员
We rep six first-round NBA picks.
代言协议已经带来超过三千两百万...
Endorsement deals have brought in well over $32 million...
不错  我们就拿这个开场
Impressive. We'll lead with that.
体育是投资者们的最爱  各位
Sports is an investor favorite, ladies and gentlemen.
能让气氛热烈起来  激发活力
It gets the crowd revved up and energized.
不  我们要用音乐开场
No, we will lead with music.
帝国娱乐至始至终都是主打音乐
Empire begins and ends with music.
永远不要忘了这点
Never forget that.
这场展示演出是关于资金的  爸
This presentation's about money, Dad.
席勒那样的人想听到的是数字
Men like Schiller want to hear the numbers.
音乐才会让他们掏出腰包
Music is what's gonna get them
给公司投资大笔资金
to invest their millions in this company.
音乐能够动情
Music is emotional.
音乐是帝国娱乐的根本
Music is what Empire's about.
我想听听看这次音乐的演出阵容
I want to hear the music lineup.
好的
Lovely.
在开场前的鸡尾酒会上
We have multiple acts that will be doing
我们准备了几场表演
for the pre-show cocktail party.
接着会以哈基姆和贾马尔的合唱正式开场
And then Hakeem and Jamal are gonna be opening on the main stage.
不  不
No, no, no, no, no!
我要艾儿·达拉斯开场
I want to open with Elle Dallas--
她是继我之后
she was Empire's first
帝国娱乐的第一位白金唱片歌手
platinum-selling artist after me.
她能在这帮有钱人面前打好感情牌
She'll have a sentimental appeal to this money crowd.
我也很希望艾儿出场  卢修斯
I would love to have Elle, Lucious.
但她是个瘾君子
But she's an addict.
琦琦说她现在状态不错
Well, Cookie says she's in good shape.
这事我信琦琦
I trust Cookie on this.
好吧
Fine.
♪We got to move these color TVs♪
好
Okay.
♪We are the people who turn illegal to legal♪
♪We take the good with the evil♪
♪Create more sales than the Beatles♪
♪And the Lion's our logo, we the sharks in the water♪
♪Multimedia moguls♪
♪More offices than the Oval♪♪Let's go♪
♪We do everything, came up in the game♪
♪Necessary♪♪Finish it by any means necessary♪
♪We everywhere-- millionaires, billionaires, visionaires♪
♪Back to bidness, let's expand think ahead to sell the brand♪
♪We got to install microwave ovens♪
-你挡着我了  -把麦克风还给我
- You stepping in my way, man! - Give me my damn mic!
我只想确保我们不像你这么松懈
I'm just trying to make sure that we ain't lagging like you!
你是想抢我的风头
Nah, you trying to steal my spotlight.
那可不难做到
Well, that ain't hard to do.
我这才叫表演
It's called a performance.
-你怎么不学学表演  -哥不干了
- Why don't you learn to perform? - I’m not doing it.
-哥不干了  -那就别啊  傻逼
- I’m not doing it. - Then don't do it, fool.
你俩给老娘闭嘴
Shut up, both of y'all!
你们两个小自私鬼今晚就消停一会
One night of your little selfish lives!
你们的哥哥安德鲁
Now, your brother Andre is out there
正在那里费尽心思地拉拢金主们
trying to hustle up big-time investors,
努力让你们的父亲美梦成真
trying to make your father's dream come true!
他此时此刻正在拼老命地努力
And he worked his ass off for this moment right here, right now!
为了这次演出和你们两个不识好歹的东西
Fought his way like a dog out of the projects
做牛做马
for you two ingrates!
为了你父亲唯一的夙愿
Now, can you please come together,
拜托你们就团结这一次
for this one thing your father needs,
让他把这件最终还是你们受益的事促成
so he can bring this thing home for you!
听到没
You hear me?
我问你听到没
I said do you hear me?
哈基姆
Hakeem!
听你母亲的
Listen to your mother!
她是个非常智慧的女人
Very wise woman.
你们休息一会
Y'all take a minute.
你不躺床上来这里干什么
What are you doing out of bed?
只是食物中毒
It was just food poisoning.
"食物中毒"吗
"Food poisoning," Huh?
你到底怎么了  卢修斯
What's really going on with you, Lucious?
我没事
I'm fine.
刚刚你说得真好
They were some really nice words you said there.
卢修斯  你那伤心情歌就免了
Lucious, save your little sad songs.
我没时间听
I don't have time for them.
这哥俩碍到我赚钱了
Those boys was coming between me and my money.
我只是做了我该做的
I just did what I had to do.
麦迪逊大道3353号
是  我们要重点注意
Yeah, we just keep a eye out
-几个新艺人  -马尔科姆先生
- for just new artists... - Mr. Malcolm!
电梯好像卡在17楼
The elevator seems to be stuck
大概有十分钟了
on 17 for, like, the last ten minutes.
能帮我吗
Can you help me out?
最近好吗
How are you?
不错  你呢
I'm good. How you doing?
还行
I'm good.
我试试看
Let's see what I can do.
好了  开始动了
There it is. It's moving.
我找不到妈妈了
I lost my mommy.
她丢下孩子就不见了吗
So, she just up and left her child?
没错  好像是这样的
Yeah, it appears that way.
我们搜了整幢楼
We searched the entire building.
贾马尔要当甜心老爸了吗
Jamal gonna be a daddy?
-谁想得到啊  -别烦我
- Who'd-a thunk? - Leave me with all that.
-贾马尔  -我没事  别管我
- Jamal! - I’m fine. Leave me alone.
-怎么了  -给我点时间想想
- What? - I just need time to think.
让他走  他需要发泄一下
No, let him go. He needs to blow off some steam.
现在那小女孩在哪
Where's the little girl at now?
都怪你  卢修斯
This is your fault, Lucious!
怎么怪我
Why is this my fault?!
她人呢
Where is she?
贝基带着她  很安全  先生
She's safe with Becky, sir.
-今晚玩得开心  先生  -谢谢
- Have a good evening, sir. - Thank you.
不用谢
You're welcome.
她不在自己公寓
She ain't at her apartment.
家人也没见过她
Family hasn't seen her, either.
要联系卖她毒品的人吗
Did you call her dealers?
接电话  艾儿  求你了
Oh, come on, Elle, please!
别这样对我  今晚可不行  拜托了
Don't do this to me. Not tonight, please.
事儿逼小姐就希望这样
You know, Miss Thing gonna love this.
艾儿让你在卢修斯面前丢脸
Elle making you look like a fool to Lucious.
我问你的意见了吗
Did I ask for your opinion?
你有点管不住自己的嘴啊
You know, you getting a little too loose in the lips.
-有人在叫我吗  -艾儿  天呐
- Did I hear my name? - Elle, my God!
-完全没吸毒  -你真美
- And I'm clean. - You look amazing!
抱歉吓着你了  但我需要练习
I'm so sorry to scare you, but I need to rehearse.
在帝国娱乐待久了  也过上"CP"时间了
I've been around Empire so long, I'm on CP time.
是说有色人种爱迟到
Colored People time.
♪Don't look at me that Way♪
♪Like you know how it's going to end♪
♪'Cause I'm too tired to be honest♪
♪And I'm too hurt♪
♪To pretend♪
♪Darling, some wounds will not mend♪
♪Walk out on me♪
♪I'll see you for the last time♪
♪Walk out on me, walk out on me♪
♪I'm giving you a life line♪
♪Say so long♪
♪And then walk away♪
这是爸爸  这是妈妈
This is the daddy, this is the mommy.
他们走进了房子
They do all walk in the house.
从此幸福地生活在一起
Then they live happy ever after.
那只能是愿望了
Good luck with that.
你说厨师来不了了是什么意思
What do you mean the chef bailed?
那是我爸爸
That's my daddy.
我知道
I know.
那就找戈登·拉姆齐[顶级厨师]
Then call Gordon Ramsay.
我本来也一直在跟他谈
I've been talking to him
接管拉维提科斯厨房的事
about taking over the kitchen at Laviticus anyway.
行  赶快办好
Yeah, get it done.
贝基一直在照顾你女儿
You know, Becky's been taking care of your daughter.
你应该去谢谢她
You might want to thank her for that.
你怎么这么确定她是我女儿
What makes you so sure she's my daughter?
你和她母亲结婚了
You were married to her mother.
我和她的婚姻只是个幌子  你知道的
Our marriage was a sham. You know that.
别闹了
Quit being so dramatic.
我当时是想保护你
I did it to try and protect you.
你前途无量
You-you-you had a promising career,
你那天上节目
and it's the same thing you did
也是这么做的
the other day on the radio.
这样做很明智  贾马尔
It's the smart thing to do, Jamal.
你有首大热新单曲
I mean, you got a hot new single.
现在是紧要关头
A lot at stake.
你能做那个决定我很欣赏
I respect you for that decision.
迈克尔走了
Michael left.
我听说了
Yeah, I heard.
真遗憾
I'm sorry.
省省吧
Please.
好吧
Okay...
我并不因为他走感到遗憾
I'm not sorry he's gone.
但我遗憾你不开心
I am sorry that you're not happy.
你总有一天会遇到一个
Eventually, you're gonna meet somebody
懂得和艺人在一起
who really understands what it's like to...
是什么感觉的人
be with an artist.
这很难
It's hard.
贾马尔  你觉得有没有一丝可能
Jamal, you think there's a possibility
这个小女孩真是你女儿
that this little girl might really be your daughter?
弗农派人去外面
Vernon's got people combing the street,
想办法找她母亲
trying to find her mother.
我和安妮卡暂时先接她回家
In the interim, Anika and I can take her home.
我们叫来了胡安妮塔
We got Juanita over there.
她肯定很乐意照看她
She'll get a kick out of looking after her.
你不是在孤军奋战
You're not on your own here.
♪Empire state of mind♪
♪Let's go♪♪Things are looking up♪
♪I'm ready for tonight♪
♪I feel good, real good♪
♪Can't nobody hold me down♪
♪Take advantage of♪
♪All these flashin' lights♪
♪Cause it's the best time, the best time for it♪
♪We can do it♪♪All right now♪
♪Can't nobody♪♪Tie me down♪
♪If you want it I got it♪
♪Tomorrow's not promised♪
♪So live inside the moment♪
♪Tell me what we waiting for♪
♪What the hell are waiting for♪
♪I wanna live inside the moment♪
这是马文·蒙切尔  这是艾儿·达拉斯
Marvin Menchel, Elle Dallas.
你就是马文·蒙切尔
It's, uh... Marvin Menchel!
见到你很荣幸
It's, uh... It-it's an honor.
你这个性感猛男
Oh, you sexy beast!
艾儿  你气色真好
Elle, you look amazing.
安妮卡  你真美
Anika, you look beautiful.
你也很美
Lovely yourself.
请带她上楼
Take her upstairs, please.
她怎么样
How's she doing?
她状态应该不错
She's doing fine, I guess.
说她愿意跟我去任何聚会...
Says she wants to go any meeting with me, so...
很好  走着瞧吧
Good. We'll see about that.
艾科伙伴公司主要投资科技公司
Okay, Echo Partners invests in technology companies.
帝国娱乐2015年投资商展示演出
他们资助了"好好听"音乐分享手机应用
They funded the Listen Up Music sharing app.
就在那边
Right over here.
-兄弟  -幸会
- Young brother. - A pleasure.
谢谢你抽空前来
Thank you so much for being here.
这位女士是《华尔街日报》的记者
This woman is a reporter from the Wall Street Journal.
你好
How are you?
好的
Okay...
需要休息一下吗
Hey, do you need a break?
不了  我没事
No, no. I'm fine.
你真没事吗
You okay?
还有谁
Well, who else?
好吧  那边是...
Uh, Well, right over there we have, uh...
-贾马尔让我喝这种绿茶  -给你
- Jamals got me drinking this green tea stuff. - Here you go.
感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
你说我什么感觉
How do you think I'm feeling?
我好紧张  亲爱的
I'm feeling nervous, darling,
我好紧张
I'm feeling nervous.
我只是  不想让你失望
I just... I don't want to let you down.
你不会的  你不会的
You won't. You won't.
大家都很高兴你能来  艾儿
Everybody's so happy you're here, Elle.
你的音乐很棒
The buzz is amazing.
我得去看看我儿子们
You know what? I'm gonna go check on my sons.
我马上回来
Be right back.
你好  艾儿
Hi, Elle.
今晚的舞台之星啊
The star of the show tonight.
你好吗
How you doing?
很好  谢谢
Fine, thanks.
我知道我们一直没什么交流的机会
I-I know we haven't had a chance to talk much,
但我还是想来说一声
but I just wanted to take some time to tell you
你能来我真的很高兴
how happy I am that you're here.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚对你来说很重要
It's a big night for you.
如果一个月前
Yeah, if you'd have told me a month ago
你跟我说我还能登台表演
I was going to be performing again...
我肯定不信
I wouldn't have believed you.
但是琦琦却做到了
But Cookie pulled this all together.
是啊
She did.
艾儿  能跟你合个影吗
Ooh, Elle, can I get a selfie with you?
-当然  -太好了
- Of course. - All right.
-谢谢  -不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
真见鬼
Aw, shoot.
抱歉  我得走了
I'm sorry. I have to go.
但是  亲  你要震撼全场哦
But, girl, knock 'em dead.
谢谢你
Thank you so much.
你不喝酒吗
You're not drinking?
今晚我不喝
Nah, I ain't drinking tonight.
过会儿再找你  哥
I'm gonna holla at you later, B.
《利尼里亚女郎》也是迈克尔·杰克逊一首单曲的名字
那位利比里亚女郎是谁
Who is that Liberian girl over there?
卡米拉·马克斯  英国布里坦尼卡股份公司
Uh, Camilla Marks. Brittanica Holdings under the UK.
主要投资
Mainly invests in...
广告和营销公司
advertising and marketing firms.
很高兴你能来  马克斯女士
Pleasure to have you here, Ms. Marks.
谢谢
Thank you.
希望你会喜欢今晚的演出
Hope you're enjoying what you're seeing today.
我想我会的
I expect I will.
我对帝国的新兴艺人很有兴趣
I'm extremely interested in Empire's exciting young talent roster.
是吗
Do tell.
我的人说您儿子哈基姆很有天分
Well, my people tell me your son Hakeem is very talented
一定会成为巨星
and is destined for superstardom.
我也希望如此
I hope so.
现在我知道这天分是遗传谁的了
And I can see why he's so talented.
你这么说我可要脸红了
You're gonna make me blush.
我得走了  希望能再见
I have to go. I hope to see you again.
今晚玩得开心
Have a good night.
♪Walk out on me♪
♪Alone there and walk away♪
♪Say... so long♪
♪Walk away♪
♪Walk out on me♪
♪See you for the last time♪
♪On me♪
艾儿
Elle.
我到处找你
I've been looking for you everywhere.
-我就在这里啊  -你没事吧
- I'm right here, man. - Are you okay?
不行不行  不能抽烟
Oh, no, no, no. No cigarettes.
需要你的声音  你要唱歌
We need our voice. We need our voice.
我会陪着你  走吧  马上要开场了
I'll be with you... Come on, We're ready, we're ready to start.
-怎么了  -你嗑药了吗
- What? - Are you high?
感觉是有点怪  但我什么也没嗑
I feel weird, but I didn't take anything.
琦琦  我没事
Cookie, I'm fine.
-只是有点头晕  -我还为你做了担保
- I'm just a little woozy. - I vouched for you.
-我是头晕  -当着卢修斯的面  可恶
- I'm a little woozy. - With Lucious, damn it!
现在我得去告诉他你这样没法唱了
I gotta go tell him that you cannot perform like this!
真是浪费我的时间
Wasted my damn time.
我可以唱的  琦琦  我可以唱
I can sing... Cookie, I can sing your damn song!
你给我闭嘴
Shut up talking!
不能让你来开场了
We gotta start the show without you.
你要...
You are going to...
-让开  -兄弟
- Move your ass. - Yo, man...
给我坐下
Sit your ass down.
怪人
Weirdo.
借下喷雾  哥们  闪开
Let me use your spray, dawg. Get out of here.
卢修斯
Lucious...
我很抱歉
Look, I'm sorry, man,
我不该相信瘾君子会戒毒
I-I shouldn't have trusted a junkie to stay clean.
-怎么了  -艾儿嗑药了  没法上台
- What happened? - Elle. She's high-- she can't go on.
我就知道会这样
I knew this was gonna happen.
搞什么
Yo, man!
衣服给我  把我的夹克给我
Give me the jacket. Give me my super jacket.
过来  我需要跟你们谈谈
Hey, come here, I need to talk to y'all now.
赶紧准备  你们马上就要登台
You're gonna need to get ready; Y'all up next.
得让你们开场了
You're in the star spot.
等等  那艾儿呢
Wait, what about Elle?
别管艾儿了  她是过去时
Forget Elle. That's the past.
投资商来这里
These investors are here
是为了帝国的未来
about the future of Empire,
那就是我的儿子们
and that's my sons-- whatever beef
不管你们有什么过节  都给我暂停
y'all got going on between y'all, y'all gonna stop it.
给我出去让那些富翁心甘情愿地掏钱投资
Get out there and make those billionaires open up their checkbooks.
你们都听到爸爸的话了  快
You heard your father. come on.
好了  握手言和
Come on, shake hands.
今晚可不是关于你的  哈基姆
Tonight ain't about you, Hakeem.
这才是我儿子们
My boys.
感谢大家能够前来
Thank you so much for being here.
希望你们多少了解了一下我们公司
I hope you've all had a chance to learn a little bit about our company,
希望你们
and I hope you got a chance
跟这里不同部门的各位优秀高管
to talk to some of the very talented heads
都交谈过了
of our many different divisions.
不过此刻  在我向大家
But right now, before I come out here
展示帝国的经济实力前
and highlight Empire's financial strengths,
我要请你们放下手中的帝国杂志
I'm gonna ask you to put down your Empire magazine,
卷起你们的帝国牛仔裤
you roll up your Empire jeans,
踢掉你们的帝国鞋
kick back in your Empire footwear,
再喝一杯帝国最佳香槟
have another glass of Empire's best champagne,
再听几首帝国娱乐最优秀
and listen to a few of The Empire's
最有天赋的音乐家的作品
beautifully bad-ass, gifted musical artists,
让他们带你领略帝国娱乐的风采
and let them get you where you're supposed to be.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
掌声有请
I want you to give it up
两位极具天赋的青年才俊
to two talented and wickedly gifted young men,
恰巧也是我的儿子们
who just happen to be my sons,
帝国的未来
the future of The Empire...
哈基姆和贾马尔
Hakeem and Jamal...
里昂
Lyon...!
♪I want my MTV♪
♪Consumers♪
♪Silver spooners♪
♪It's nothin', we get money for it♪
♪Mal♪
♪Commas and zeroes♪
♪That's the way we do it♪
♪We make it work in this economy♪♪We Lyons♪
♪Roll in dinero♪
♪Pockets stay polluted♪
♪Money is dirty and we don't play clean♪
♪We chasin' paper, run, hurry, move it♪
♪Get out the way if you ain't 'bout that green♪
♪Intensive labor, taxes are included♪
♪Money is dirty and we don't play clean♪
♪We got to install microwave ovens♪
♪Yeah, we do♪
♪Custom kitchen deliveries♪
♪We gotta move these♪
♪Refrigerators♪♪Yeah, we do♪
♪We gotta move these color TVs♪
♪We are the people♪
♪Who turn illegal to legal♪
♪We take the good with the evil♪
♪Create more sales than the Beatles♪
♪And the Lion's our logo♪
♪We're the sharks in the water♪
♪Multimedia moguls, more offices♪
♪Than the Oval, we do everything♪♪Let's go♪
♪Do everything♪
♪Came up in the game to entertain♪
♪Finish it by any means necessary♪
♪We everywhere, millionaires♪
♪Billionaires, visionaries♪
♪Back to bidness, let's expand♪
♪Think ahead to sell the brand♪
♪We got to install microwave ovens♪
♪Yeah, we do♪♪Custom kitchen deliveries♪
♪We gotta move these refrigerators♪♪Yeah, we do♪
♪We gotta move these color TVs♪
♪Move dat work, move dat work♪
♪Commercialize, commercialize♪
♪Get that work, get that work♪
♪To advertise, to advertise♪
♪Make it work, make it work♪
♪Look mom, I'm on TV♪
♪Hi, mom, I'm on TV♪
♪My talents worth a fortune♪
♪Five hunnit♪
♪They know that I'm a boss♪
♪I got the highest portion♪
♪I'm all about my bidness♪
♪All about my money♪
♪My talents worth a fortune♪
♪Five hunnit♪
♪Hot damn it, I'm a boss♪
♪I got the highest portion♪
♪I'm all about my bidess♪
♪Yeah, I'm all about my bidness♪
琦琦
Cookie...
-怎么了  -跟我过来
- What?! - Come here!
♪You know what it is♪
♪Jamal... Hakeem♪
我说不出...说不出话
I can't... I can't talk.
需要什么吗  老兄  你可以呼吸吗
What you need, man? Can you breathe?
我得出去致辞
I need to go out and give this speech.
我不能让你那么做
I can't let you do that, okay?
绝对不行
It's not gonna happen.
宝贝  我去就行
Look, baby, I got it.
好吗  我知道你的演讲稿
Okay? I know the speech.
那是我写的  我倒背如流
I wrote it. I know it back to front.
我甚至都不用提词机
I don't even need the teleprompters, okay?
这件事根本不需要讨论
I can't believe we're even having this discussion.
-我们不是在讨论  -应该由我代表
- We're not having a conversation. - That should be me out there.
他都不舒服了
Something is wrong with him.
你没事吧  卢修斯
Are you okay, Lucious?
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
因为外头有十亿资金等着...
Because there's a billion dollars in capital waiting out there...
蒙切尔  有什么问题吗  听着
Menchel, what's wrong with you? Okay, look,
没有问题  好吗  卢修斯擅长做秀
there's no problem, okay? Lucious is a showman--
他正在培养观众的期待感
he's building up anticipation.
出去
Look, go out there,
-打好领带  准备看秀  -先生  这边请
- fix your tie, get ready for the show. - Sir, come this way, sir.
出去等着
Just go out and do it.
儿子  我知道你想帮我
Look, I know you want to help me, son.
而这篇稿是你写的
And you wrote this thing,
不过我需要能振奋人心的人
but I need someone that can go and excite...
这个人是  琦琦
this people, Cookie.
我要你出去提醒大家
I need you to go out there and remind them
帝国娱乐是为了我们的儿子
that Empire is a family business
而建立的家族企业
built for our sons.
而且会一代接一代地传承下去
And it is gonna pass from one generation to the next generation.
永远掌握在家族手中  拜托了
It's gonna stay in the family. Please.
好
Okay.
我要去起诉那个梅森医生
I'm gonna sue that Dr. Mason.
这不是药物导致的
It's not the drugs...
什么
What?
不是药物导致的  是渐冻症
It's not the drugs, it's ALS.
-是...  -等一下  慢慢说  宝贝
- It's-it's... - Wait a minute, take your time, baby.
不是药物导致的吗
It's not the drugs that did this to you?
这和我手抖一样  会...
It's like a tremor with my hands; it will...
没事的
pass.
会...没事的
It'll... it'll pass.
卢修斯在哪里
Where's Lucious?
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
帝国娱乐的现有目标
是在接下来的财政年度里
实现30%的收益增长
孩子  我才不会读这个...
Child, I ain't readin'...
妈妈  好好照提词机念
Just read the teleprompter, mom.
我是琦琦·里昂
My name is Cookie Lyon.
我和我的前夫卢修斯  在费城西部最糟糕的
My ex-husband, Lucious, and I started this company
一处贫民窟的一个小车库里开创了这间公司
in a little garage in one of the worst ghettos in West Philadelphia.
你们中肯定有人也有那么几个前妻
Some of y'all probably have a few ex-wives, so...
所以你们知道我不会
so you know I'm not gonna be
站在这里跟你们说我前夫如何出色
standing up here telling you all this mushy stuff
这种伤感的话
about what a fine man my ex is.
她到底在说什么
What the hell's she doing?
卢修斯·里昂
Lucious Lyon...
是个音乐大神
is a musical god...
也是个心怀梦想的混蛋疯子
and he's also a crazy son of a bitch that had a dream.
他现在仍旧心怀梦想
Still has a dream--
而且谁都最好别阻碍
and nobody better ever try
卢修斯追求他的梦想
to get in between Lucious and his dreams.
我们曾以骗人为生
We were hustlers.
我们别无他选
Only choice we had.
但你们知道骗人的第一守则是什么吗
But... do you know what the first rule of hustling is?
供应与需求
Supply and demand.
这是谁说的
Hey, who said that?
没错  宝贝
That's right, baby.
聪明的男人
Smart man.
没错  建立你自己的客户群
That's right-- you create your own customer base.
让他们尝点甜头
Give them some of that good stuff.
让他们想要得到更多
Make 'em want more.
卢修斯把它用到了音乐上
You see, Lucious did that with music.
他创造了  一种曲风
He created... a sound.
人们管它叫"卢修斯·里昂之声"
They call it the "Lucious Lyon sound."
你们都知道的  否则你们不会出现在这里
You all know it, or else you wouldn't be here.
卢修斯的音乐成为了街头主流
Lucious's music took the street mainstream,
也让主流音乐感受到了街头魅力
and made the mainstream feel street.
卢修斯碰过的所有东西
Everything Lucious touches
都从石头变成了黄金  是不争的事实
turns to platinum, and that's a fact.
他在音乐领域展开事业
He started out doing it with the music.
然后他涉足
Next he did it with over a dozen
十多个赚钱的娱乐领域和销售领域
profitable entertainment and merchandise divisions.
现在...
And now...
他将用你们的钱去生钱...
he's gonna do it with your money...
只要你们够幸运  够聪明
if you're lucky enough and smart enough
把钱交给他
to put it in his hands.
我被卢修斯抛弃前
Lucious and I had three sons
我们生了三个儿子
before he dumped me.
长子安德鲁是这间公司的首席财务官
Our oldest son Andre is the CFO of this company.
他才华横溢
He's brilliant,
他会让你们每个人都赚得瓢满钵溢
and he's gonna make every last one of you filthy rich.
另外两个儿子  贾马尔和哈基姆·里昂
Our other two sons, Jamal and Hakeem Lyon...
他们真正证明了
they are living proof...
帝国娱乐绝非只是一个男人的梦想
that Empire is more than just one man's dream.
而是个能实现的梦想...
It's a dream come true...
准备要传给下一代
that's ready to be passed down to the next generation...
下下一代  再下一代
and the next and the next,
而你们...
and you all...
都能参与其中
can be a part of it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我爱你  琦琦
I love you, Cookie.
让人印象深刻啊  卢修斯
Very impressive, Lucious.
尤其是你前妻说的故事
Especially that story that your ex-wife told.
不过  真正促使我下决定的是
Oh. What really sold me, though,
你的每个家人都为了这间公司的未来
is your family and how devoted each and every one of them is
在努力奉献自己的力量
to the future of this company.
非常感谢  特里
Thank you so much, Terry.
-宝贝  -你确定
- Oh, baby... - Are you sure
我不用取消我的芝加哥之行吗
you don't want me to cancel my trip to Chicago?
拉娜会理解的
Lana's gonna understand.
不用取消
No, don't cancel. I mean,
不管刚才怎么回事  现在都没事了
whatever that is, it's gone now.
我百分百确定
I'm, like, I'm a hundred percent.
你得敲定出
Look, and you need to hammer out
她合同中的一些新细节
the new details of that contract for her.
别忘了她的律师也会在飞机上  好吗
Don't forget,her lawyer's gonna be on the plane, too, okay?
好吧  如果有情况你一定要打电话给我
All right. Well, you've got to call me if something goes down.
你到了给我打电话
You call me when you get there.
不用你来告诉我要做什么
Don't tell me what to do.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you too.
走吧
Come on.
她去哪
Where's she going?
她得连夜去芝加哥
She has to go up to Chicago overnight,
处理拉娜·德雷[打雷姐]的事情
take care of something with Lana Del Rey.
你到底告不告诉我你怎么了
Are you gonna tell me what's going on with you, or what?
我说
Yeah.
洛拉  跟安德鲁伯伯和朗达婶婶说晚安
Lola, say good night to Uncle Andre and Aunt Rhonda.
晚安  宝贝
Aw, good night, baby.
-真好看  -谢谢
- Pretty. - Thank you.
-晚安  -别忘了还有哈基姆叔叔
- Good night. - Don't forget about your Uncle Hakeem.
好看
Pretty.
真有品位
Well, she got taste.
-给我  给我  -别闹了
- Give me that, give me that. - Stop.
你会吓着她的  别闹了
You're gonna scare her. Stop.
好了  稍后给你回电
All right, I'm gonna call you back.
来吧  让她留在这里
Come here. Let her stay...
妈妈  给
Mom, here. Oh. Okay.
我不知道怎么带孩子
I don't know how to do all this.
别担心  亲爱的  他会学会的
Don't worry, sweetie, he'll get the hang of it.
我准备好提案再和你讨论
So I'll get back to you with a proposal.
同时  我会随时待命
In the meantime, I'll be standing by.
你们俩谋划什么呢
What are you two scheming up?
我们在讨论新安装的
Oh, we're talking about the new security system
安保系统
we're having installed.
凯夫拉材质墙壁
Kevlar-lined walls,
红外摄像头
infrared cameras,
地堡
a bunker...
那里将会变成无法攻破的堡垒
Place is gonna be an impenetrable fortress.
德沃先生  我在想
You know, Mr. Deveaux, I was thinking
也许我需要... 加强我那里的安全
maybe I need to... Oh, beef up the security at my place,
因为  你知道  我一个人住
because, you know, I live alone.
先生  数字结果出来  我会来找你
Sir, I'll get those numbers and get back to you.
你应该给我打电话  我们可以安排一下
You should call me so we can set that up.
你知道...
You realize...
闭嘴  卢修斯
Shut up, Lucious.
胡安妮塔  把孩子带上楼
Juanita, take the baby upstairs.
好的  先生
Yes, sir.
给我吧
Excuse me.
哈基姆
Hakeem...
坐下
Have a seat.
等等
Hold up.
我的小家伙
Mm! My little gangsta!
我病了
I'm sick.
等等  什么意思
Wait, what-what do you mean?
我患了渐冻症
I have ALS.
肌萎缩性脊髓侧索硬化症
Amyotrophic lateral sclerosis.
这是一种
It is a...
极具侵略性的
an aggressive
退化性神经肌肉障碍
and degenerative neuromuscular disorder
最终将会夺走我控制身体的
that will eventually take away my ability to control...
能力
my body.
今晚发生的事情
What happened tonight is, uh...
意味着症状变严重了
it means the symptoms are getting worse.
这是绝症  无药可医
It's fatal. There's no cure.
那我们还搞这些干什么
Then why are we even doing this?
-今晚的演出还这么大阵仗  -这是...
- That monster show we put on today. - That was...
我留给你们的遗产
My legacy for you.
所以我一直这么拼命地逼迫你们
I mean, that's why I've been pushing y'all so hard.
我为你们今晚的表现骄傲
I was so proud of y'all tonight.
谁知道这事
Who knows this? Hm?
弗农  贝基
Vernon, Becky...
当然还有安妮卡
and, uh, Anika, of course.
首次公开募股的事  我们得制定个计划
Well, the IPO-- we... We have to have a plan.
他快要死了  你却在操心首次公开募股
He's dying and you're worrying about a IPO?
-我该揍你  -哈基姆  哈基姆
- Yo, I should knock you... - Hakeem! Hakeem!
我揍你这个小混蛋
Beat your little ass!
-得了吧  -住手  坐下
- Come on! - Stop! Sit down!
他有资格难受
He should be upset.
-走  我们回家  -我不知道怎么办
- Come on, baby, we got to go home. - I don't know what to do.
-安德鲁  安德鲁  看着我  -干什么
- Andre, Andre, look at me. - What?!
我不需要你帮忙
I don't need your help!
抱歉  卢修斯
I'm sorry, Lucious.
我并不想这样  儿子
It's not what I wanted, son.
-妈  -孩子们来  我们聊聊
- Ma... - Boys, come on, let's talk for a minute.
你们都经历了许多事情
Y'all have been through a lot.
但不管发生什么  你们都会挺过去
But y'all gonna get through this, whatever happens.
现在我需要你们坚强起来
Right now I need y'all to be strong.
我们会的  老爸
We will, dad.
尽管告诉我们你需要什么
Just tell us what you need.
你们妈妈不太能接受
Your mama didn't take this well.
我需要和她单独待会  好吗
I need a moment with her, okay?
你们都回家吧  好吗
Y'all go on home, okay?
安德鲁
Andre...
宝贝  你在干什么
Baby, what are you doing?
宝贝  安德鲁  怎么了
Baby...? Andre, what's Wrong?
宝贝  别这样  看着我
Baby, stop it. Look at me.
宝贝  别这样  深呼吸
Baby... Stop... Breathe...
看着我  宝贝
Look at me, baby.
你会接管这家公司的
You're gonna run this company.
你会得到你为之奋斗的一切  好吗
You're gonna have everything you've ever worked for, okay?
看着我
Look at me.
记得这首歌吗
Remember this?
你今晚在那里  为我说了不少好话
You said some really, really nice things about me up there tonight.
让我感觉挺好的
Kind of made me feel good.
特别是听到你那么说
Especially hearing that from you.
你为什么表现得很惊讶
Why are you acting so surprised?
因为  我说不清
Because, I don't know...
我只是感觉我欠你
I just feel like I owe you.
你有什么欠我的  卢修斯
Why do you have to owe me, Lucious?
这也是我的梦想  记得吗
This was my dream, too, remember?
是的  但我是说  你...
Yeah. But I mean, you...
在我之前就遇见到这一切了
saw this... way before I did.
甚至在我发行我的第一首单曲前  你说
Even before I hit my first single, you said
从此以后我们会彻底改变音乐行业
we were about to change the music business forever...
宝贝
Baby.
那是因为我了解你
And that's because I know you.
我清楚你的实力
I know what you're capable of.
所以你要战胜病魔  卢修斯
That's why you're gotta beat this, Lucious.
你要打败它
You're gonna beat this thing.
因为我不能再失去你了
Because I can't lose you again.
♪You got me watching you, a like a camera do♪
你现在就有我
You have me now.
我们不要浪费这一刻
Let's not lose this moment.
能请你跳一支舞吗  亲爱的
May I have this dance, my love?
♪You wear your glasses, you can't see♪
♪Girl, I love your crooked smile♪
♪Your crooked smile♪
♪Hair ain't done, you're makeup-free♪
♪You'll never go out of style♪
♪'Cause you ain't got time to pack♪
这一直都是首好歌
This was always a good song.
因为这写的是你
'Cause it was about you.
♪Way too much class, all up inside♪
你总是为我这么做
You always did it for me.
♪You should be happy with the nappy♪
♪Hot damn, have you seen them thighs♪
你从没停止过为我这么做
You never stopped doing it for me.
♪And collard greens♪
♪You call me papi, and I like it♪
♪You're so beautiful♪
♪You got me watching you, like a camera do♪
♪I'll still am a wait for you♪
♪You got feeling all kinds of ways♪
♪You're so beautiful♪
♪You got me watching you, like a camera do♪
♪I'll still wait for you♪
♪You got feeling all kinds of ways♪
♪This is the kind of song♪
♪Make a woman love a man♪
♪Woman love a man♪
♪Woman love a man and♪
♪You're so beautiful♪
♪You got me watching you♪
♪Like a camera do♪
宝贝
Babe?
♪I'll still wait for you♪
♪You got me♪
♪You're so beautiful♪
♪You got me watching you, like a camera do♪
♪I'll still wait for you♪
♪You got me feeling all kind of ways♪
[下集预告]期待更精彩